CALEB OSBORN

Computer Science

1414 Avenue D · Danbury, TX 77534	979.285.5197	csosborn@uh.edu
INTERNSHIP		
PROFILE:	Committed to a career combining formal education in practical work experience. Experience in physics, med C++ programming, as well as interpreting mechanical knowledge of power tools / lathes, and practical team-	chanics, Java, C, and I drawings, working
EDUCATION:	University Of Houston · Houston, Texas	
	Computer Science Major (August 2015-PrHonors Engineering Program (August 201	
	Practical Team-Based Lab Work:	
	Arithmetic Logic Unit ProjectInfrared Optical-Listener	 Matlab Labview
	 Expected Graduation Date: December 201 Cumulative GPA: 2.65 (includes MEC Major GPA: 3.00 (Computer Science) 	
WORK EXPERIENCE:		
	FlexElement Texas · Houston, Texas (August 2012	- Present)
	 Oil and gas industry - internship IT support, high-performance coupling ass maintenance 	sembly, inspection, and
Kelm Engineering · Friendswood, Texas (July 2012 – August 20		2 – August 2012)
	 Interpreting mechanical drawings, and expendingering 	osure to professional
ORGANIZATIONS:		
	 Triangle Fraternity (2013 – Present) Risk Management Chair (2014) Judiciary Board Member (2014) 	
	Boy Scouts of America (2005 – Present) Eagle Scout (Attained August 2010)	
INTERESTS:	Systems Optimization, Process Technology, Web Des Technology, Mechanics, Electronics, Aerospace, Avid Design, Entrepreneurship, Hunting, Fishing	O .
REFERENCES:	Available Upon Request.	